{
    "id": "658cc67bc88c44e795993003eca3eceb",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Rahul is known for his ................................. fuse. The other day he yelled at the teacher for asking him to leave the class.",
            "description": "To have a short fuse is to have quick temper.",
            "answers": [
                "quick",
                "tight",
                "short"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca2c0500821e4ad5b32f2de93e5b22d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had ........................................ in my stomach as I waited for the results to be announced.",
            "description": "When you have butterflies in your stomach, you are nervous.",
            "answers": [
                "dragons",
                "spiders",
                "butterflies"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a9d1452bd8645a9ae82de160130c9a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter made the national team by the skin of his ................................... you can tell that he hasn't fully recovered from his injuries.",
            "description": "When you make something by the skin of your teeth, you barely make it.",
            "answers": [
                "face",
                "nose",
                "teeth"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ef1d2e34c3474e2f86967b70b74afb36"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you always cry ................................., no one will be there to help you when you actually need it.",
            "description": "To cry wolf is to ask for help when you don't need it.",
            "answers": [
                "tiger",
                "fox",
                "wolf"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "587ef51a94c14a3e80b5e24fc04c1ed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cut him some ................................ After all, he is a mere child.",
            "description": "To cut someone some slack is to not judge them too harshly.",
            "answers": [
                "ice",
                "space",
                "slack"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f6d52042b17a4ed0b5d0e7be01d1c8de"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't go to the party because I was down for the .................................. after working all day in the garden.",
            "description": "When you are down for the count, you are too tired.",
            "answers": [
                "moment",
                "count",
                "hell"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "858446f0070d4daebacd7737e6f296cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know getting fired is no fun but remember that every cloud has a ....................................... lining.",
            "description": "This expression is used to mean that you can find good in every bad situation.",
            "answers": [
                "white",
                "silver",
                "golden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07ce08c13bae4f1d9962e73869ca24aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Finding a good job these days is as hard as finding a ............................................... in a haystack.",
            "description": "This expression is used to refer to something that is virtually impossible.",
            "answers": [
                "needle",
                "knife",
                "pin"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "350f7d366b784f27b2bb651de8f4db30"
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt like a ...................................... out of water at the party because I didn't know anyone there.",
            "description": "To feel like a fish out of water is to feel out of place.",
            "answers": [
                "fish",
                "frog",
                "turtle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "717058a6efc74363bfabe8ce298bb1e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have to get this off my ……………………………… - I was the person who reported you to the police.",
            "description": "To get something off your chest is to talk about something that has been bothering you for a while.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "throat",
                "chest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d567a9a21bca48b595a04f62f23bdc62"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never gone scuba diving, but I am going to give it a ....................................",
            "description": "To give it a whirl is to try something.",
            "answers": [
                "swirl",
                "whirl",
                "twirl"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccb060e6bae54e46b49b8b3f1baebce6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her career went down in .................................... after she started doing drugs.",
            "description": "To go down in flames is to fail suddenly and spectacularly.",
            "answers": [
                "arms",
                "smoke",
                "flames"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27dfe6736599423fa7913a331b2ec2c7"
        }
    ]
}